Atharva Gundawar

Deep Learning & Computer Vision Engineer

A committed, focused and creative programmer who wants to make a difference in this world. I specialize in Deep Learning and Data Analytics, along side I have some experience in App/Web development and AR. I Love to Code and build new and innovative solutions which solve real life practical problems.



- atharva.n.gundawar@gmail.com
- Pune, India
- in linkedin.com/in/atharva-gundawar-975507190
- 🔌 stackoverflow.com/users/13105973/atharva-gundawar

- 9607105448,9325397586
- atharva-gundawar.github.io/portfolio-website/
- github.com/atharva-gundawar
 - medium.com/@atharva.n.gundawar

EDUCATION

School

Indira National School

2017 - 2019 91%

College VIT Vellore

VII VCIIOIC

06/2019 - Present 8.9 CGPA

B.Tech

Computer Science

WORK EXPERIENCE

Core Committee Member of Computer Society of India

Computer Society of India

11/2019 - 07/2020 Vellore Technical member at Computer Society of India

Core Committee Member of ACM-VIT Association for Computing Machinery

11/2019 - 07/2021 Al/ML researcher at Association for Computing Machinery Vellore

Lead Data Analyst

eduMates

05/2020 - 09/2020 Pune

Analyzed Data for Universities and for eduMates and gave predictions and demographics through the data collected by the platform

Software engineer & Computer Vision engineer Tribe and Camcann

05/2020 - 11/2020 Vellore

ontribe.xyz As a part of tribe I built the Github analyzer and score predictor which is being used on their platform. camcann.com I had made a model that returns 3D locations of multiple Humans from a 2D feed. I also made an AI system that morphed jewelry on a person In realtime using VR. I helped them make a new hand detection model used in their no-touch poll system

Data Analyst and Computer Vision Engineer Blackcoffer

07/2021 - Present

Developed Pipelines for big data transfer and analysis - Optimized Neo4j database to save 40% more space - Developing Background removal and watermark removal systems

SKILLS



TOP PROJECTS

Data Analytics for 100's of collages in the UK while working for EduMates

Github Analyser, Productivity Prediction and Ranker for OnTribe

Dynamic tracking, Spoof-proof Face Recognition, Virtual Mouse and Key Control System(Computer Vision)

Prediction of 3D location of humans from a 2D feed

Al powered dynamic questioning platform, semantic segmentation, Bones and organs segmentation

Python Libraries on Pypi

Custom Dense layers models, architectures, loss functions and kernels

CERTIFICATES

Udacity Deep Learning Nanodegree

Courser NLP Specialization

Deep Learning with Pytorch: Zero to GANs

AWS Seeing Clearly: Computer Vision Theory

Deeplearning.ai Neural Networks and Deep Learning

SuperDataScience Machine Learning

LANGUAGES

Python

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

C++ and C#

Javascript

Professional Working Proficiency

Limited Working Proficiency

English

Professional Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

Al Entrepreneurship Space Business

Automation and Robotics Quantum Computing